Keep Moving Forward.
Borrowed Time is a animation, drama, western film directed by Andrew Coats.
A weathered Sheriff returns to the remains of an accident
he has spent a lifetime trying to forget.
With each step forward, the memories come flooding back.
Faced with his mistake once again, he must find the strength to carry on.
(voice), played by Greg Dykstra.
(voice), played by Nick Pitera.
(voice), played by Steve Purcell.
Borrowed Time  is a 2015 American animated Western short film
directed by Pixar artists Andrew Coats and Lou Hamou-Lhadj.
The film explores themes of police, parent child
relationship, family relationships, flashback, love.
The tone is emotional.